<subtitle>Web Platform APIs for the Present and Future</subtitle>

  <othercredit role="proofreader">
    <firstname>Sharon</firstname>
    <surname>Wilkey</surname>
  </othercredit>
  <othercredit role="illustrator">
    <firstname>Rebecca</firstname>
    <surname>Demarest</surname>
  </othercredit>

  <!-- All rights reserved. -->

  <publisher>
    <publishername>O’Reilly Media, Inc.    </publishername>
    <address format="linespecific">
      <street>1005 Gravenstein Highway North</street>
      <city>Sebastopol</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <postcode>95472</postcode>
    </address>
  </publisher>

  <legalnotice role="printlocation">
    <para>Printed in the United States of America.</para>
  </legalnotice>

  <legalnotice role="printer">
    <para>[LSI]</para>
  </legalnotice>

  <legalnotice role="use">
    <para>O’Reilly books may be purchased for educational, business, or sales promotional use. Online editions are also available for most 
          titles (<ulink url="http://my.safaribooksonline.com/?portal=oreilly" role="orm:hideurl:ital">http://my.safaribooksonline.com</ulink>). For more information, contact our corporate/institutional sales department:
          800-998-9938 or <phrase role="keep-together"><email>corporate@oreilly.com</email></phrase>.</para>
  </legalnotice>

  <legalnotice role="trademarks">
    <para>Nutshell Handbook, the Nutshell Handbook logo, and the O’Reilly logo
          are registered trademarks of O’Reilly Media, Inc. !!FILL THIS IN!!
          and related trade dress are trademarks of O’Reilly Media, Inc.    </para>
    <para>Many of the designations used by manufacturers and sellers to distinguish
          their products are claimed as trademarks. Where those designations appear
          in this book, and O’Reilly Media, Inc. was aware of a trademark claim,
          the designations have been printed in caps or initial caps.    </para>
  </legalnotice>

  <legalnotice role="damages">
    <para>While every precaution has been taken in the preparation of this book,
        the publisher and authors assume no responsibility for errors or omissions, 
        or for damages resulting from the use of the information contained herein.</para>
  </legalnotice>
<isbn>9781449370732</isbn><edition>1</edition><author><firstname>Brandon</firstname><surname>Satrom</surname><authorblurb><para>Brandon Satrom has been a web developer for close to fifteen years and have worked with countless web technologies and browsers during that time. He's worked as a Microsoft Web Evangelist, and currently serves as the Lead Program Manager for Telerik’s Cross-Platform Tools and Services, which includes Kendo UI, a library for building rich, interactive web and hybrid mobile applications with HTML, JavaScript and CSS. He co-wrote Building Windows 8 Applications with JavaScript, which was published in January of 2013.</para></authorblurb></author><editor><firstname>Simon</firstname><surname>St. Laurent</surname></editor><editor><firstname>Brian</firstname><surname>Anderson</surname></editor><copyright><year>2014</year><holder>Brandon Satrom</holder></copyright><editor role="production"><firstname>Nicole</firstname><surname>Shelby</surname></editor><othercredit role="coverdesigner"><firstname>Randy</firstname><surname>Comer</surname></othercredit><othercredit role="interiordesigner"><firstname>David</firstname><surname>Futato</surname></othercredit><printhistory><formalpara><title>First Edition</title><para>February, 2014</para></formalpara></printhistory><revhistory><revision><date>2014-02-14</date><revremark>First release</revremark></revision></revhistory><legalnotice role="perfect"><para/></legalnotice>
